Madison Wells

Computer scientist with several years of experience working in the networking and cybersecurity sector. Works well with others as well as individually. High attention to detail and a passion for organization. Strong problem-solving and time management skills. Able to learn quickly.

Education

UNC Chapel Hill

Studied BS in Computer Science

Aug 2016 - May 2019, Chapel Hill, NC

North Carolina School of Science and Mathematics

High school diploma Aug 2014 - June 2016, Durham, NC

Technical experience

Microsoft Office

Excel, Word, OneNote

Software development

Java, Bash, Python, C

Web development

HTML, CSS, JavaScript

Version control systems

Git, GitHub, GitLab

Other experience

HackNC 2017

Torp in **Java**

Worked on a team of 4 to create a battleship-esque submarine game which uses a sonar to detect nearby enemy ships.

HackNC 2018

Isometria in **JavaScript**

Worked on a team of 2 to create an isometric puzzle platformer that uses the camera's perspective to perform mind-bending MC Escher-style 3D movement.

Professional Experience

Network/Security Technician IT/OT Cybersecurity

Duke Energy Corporation

Dec 2020 - present, Charlotte, NC

Interfaces with Telecom, Firewall, and Silent Defense/Splunk engineer teams, providing high-level technical support on a variety of network hardware (Palo Alto, Cisco, Ixia, Dell, OpenGear). Troubleshooting configurations on Cisco switches and routers. Has overseen the configuration and deployment of over \$5M of equipment to-date. Handles NERC CIP secure information and IP addresses. Oversees production process from inventory through final shipment.

Office Assistant

Food Lion

Apr 2020 - Oct 2020, Feb 2018- Aug 2018, Denver, NC

Managed customer service, assisting with a large variety of customers. Handled accounting work with an average \$30k/day, sorting and organizing. Managed and provided supervisory resources to storefront employees.

Technical Operations Intern

TKXS

Oct 2019 - Jan 2020, Raleigh, NC

Provided technical support, software installation, configuration, and troubleshooting around the office. Reorganized hardware and fixed old computers (desktops, laptops, etc.). Performed Bash script programming involving Heroku and AWS integration.

IT Walk-in Technician

ITS @ University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill

Jan 2019 - Aug 2019, Chapel Hill, NC

Worked at walk-in IT service desk at UNC Chapel Hill providing customer service and troubleshooting clients' computers. Performed malware removal/cleanup. General software maintenance (removing slow software, providing updates, etc.). Assisted with hardware troubleshooting. Provided software installation.

Residential Computing Consultant

ResNET University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill

Aug 2017 - Dec 2017, Chapel Hill, NC

Provided on-site tech support for UNC residential students. Provided security expertise and connectivity assistance among other ad-hoc services. Assisted residents with malware removal, set-up of new devices, connecting devices to the University's WiFi, and more. Helped students connect with and understand technology by engaging in explanatory tech sessions. Hosted events involving ResNET-owned equipment and technology.

Data Transfer Clerk

First Residential Services

May 2017 - Jul 2017, Charlotte, NC

Performed back-end data processing on large quantities of data. Trained in proper privacy-first policies for handling sensitive customer information. Minor VBA programming in Excel for management of massive spreadsheets.